favado.com 2016-06-23

# Privacy Policy - Favado App

INTRODUCTION. Savings.com, Inc. (“Savings.com”, “us”, “our” or “we”) has developed this Privacy Policy which details important information regarding the use and disclosure of user information collected on the website Savings.com which is owned and operated by Savings.com, and any other websites owned and operated by Savings.com, ( the “Site”). Each Site has adopted this Privacy Policy to the extent applicable. This Privacy Policy also applies to the use and disclosure of information collected when you download, install and use the Savings.com browser extensions and the services made available through those browser extensions (collectively, the “Browser Extensions”), or use any other interactive properties, including but not limited to our mobile applications or to those related to our social media pages or accounts (the Site, the Browser Extensions and other Savings.com interactive properties are collectively referred to herein as the “Savings.com Applications”). Savings.com provides this Privacy Policy to help you make an informed decision about whether to use, continue to use the services provided by Savings.com and/or assessed through the Savings.com Applications (“Services”). This Privacy Policy applies to your use of (1) the Savings.com Applications (however accessed and/or used, whether via personal computers, mobile devices or otherwise); (2) email or electronic catalogs and newsletters; and (3) any other means or applications in which you connect with us or our products and services.This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to our Terms of Service and the Savings.com DealFinder License Agreement. Each time that you access or use Savings.com Applications or our Services you signify that you have read, understand, and agree to be bound by the Terms of Service, and this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy, you must discontinue using the Savings.com Applications or Services.

## I. INFORMATION WE COLLECT

### Connecting with the Savings.com Applications and Information Provided by You

Contacting Us. When you provide us with information in connection with a particular activity or otherwise sign up for our Services or provide your contact information, including an email address or telephone number in connection with that activity, product or service, you agree that this action constitutes a purchase or inquiry establishing a business relationship with us. You expressly consent to our communicating with you about Savings.com using the information you provided to us. You also attest that you have the legal authority over any telephone number you provide to us and can provide us with the authorization to contact you. This means we may contact you, in person or by recorded message, by e-mail, telephone and/or mobile telephone number (including use of automated dialing equipment), text (SMS) message, or any other means of communication that your wireless or other telecommunications device may be capable of receiving.

Registration Information. We will collect personal information from you if you register on our Site or voluntarily provide information about yourself in your profile (“Personal Information”). You do not have to register to use our Services, download our Browser Extensions or access coupons on our Site. Upon initial registration you will be asked to provide a user name and zip code so we can identity your locality by city and state (“Regional Location”), or more specific location for certain applications available on Savings.com Applications, as more clearly spelled out in this policy (“Geolocation”), to serve you offers that are suited to you and where you live or are currently located. Your user name will be disclosed on all our public forums as well as your Regional Location which will be reflected by the zip code that you provide. You will have an opportunity to confirm or change your General Location without use of a zip code during the registration process. You will also have the opportunity to indicate your interests by answering questions about the types of goods and services you are interested in and your favorite brands and stores so that we can better serve you savings and offers for exactly what interests you (“Interests”). Savings.com reserves the right to deny, in its sole discretion, any user access to the Savings.com Applications or Services without notice for any or no reason.

Surveys and Promotions. From time-to-time we may request information from you and other users via surveys or contests or sweepstakes. Participation in these surveys, contests or sweepstakes is completely voluntary so you and other users have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Contact information and other information as required by the official rules may be used to notify the winners and award prizes and file winners information as required by law. Survey information will be used for the purpose(s) of the survey, including the monitoring or improvement of the use and satisfaction of Savings.com Applications.

Facebook. You may be given the option to link your Facebook account so that you can comment on the Savings.com Applications or take advantage of other features of the Savings.com Applications. When you comment on the Savings.com Applications using your Facebook username and password and clicking “allow” on the Facebook permission authorization screen, you give us permission to capture, store, use and display your Facebook user ID, your basic Facebook profile information and any other information from your Facebook profile that you specifically allow us to access. The authentication of your Facebook login credentials are conducted solely through Facebook.

Social Media Platforms. If you use Facebook or other social media platforms or applications to interact with Savings.com Applications, the social media platform(s) may have a specific privacy statement that governs the use of Personal Information related to that platform or application. In addition, we use Janrain to support our social network platforms and if you provide permission on any particular site, information from your social networking accounts may be forwarded to us. If you wish more information about how your information can be transferred to us from Janrain visit http://janrain.andculture.cc/privacy-policy/.

Geolocation Services. It is possible that we may ask you if you wish us to collect your Geolocation in order to offer you real-time deals nearby and will maintain information about your geolocation to facilitate your serving such real time deals to you. In addition, when you have the geolocation software running on your mobile phone, computer or other device, we may collect that information as controlled by your privacy settings on those Devices. We will not share your exact Geolocation or use your exact Geolocation for any other purpose.

User Generated Content. The Services may contain review or chat areas and/or other message, communication or other mechanisms designed to enable you to communicate with others or to post content on the Site (the “Interactive Services”). Please remember that any information you disclose while participating with the Interactive Services becomes public information, and is subject to redistribution by, Savings.com and all others viewing the information. You should exercise caution and discretion when deciding to disclose your personal information in a submission or posting. There is no expectation of privacy when posting, or otherwise participating on the Interactive Services. If you post content, such as messages, reviews or photos, please be aware that any personally identifiable information contained in such content is accessible to registered users or visitors to that Savings.com Application or Communication Service and we have no control over how those users may use your personally identifiable information. We have the right, but not the obligation, to monitor any activity and content associated with the Interactive Services. We reserve the right to take action in connection with any content we deem to be inappropriate. Please review our Terms of Servicefor more information regarding your appropriate use of these Interactive Services.

Framing. We use Catalina Marketing Corporation (“Catalina”) who operates Couponnetwork.com which is the Grocery section on our Site. Although the Grocery section of the Site may have a similar appearance as the Site, it is powered by Catalina and information submitted through Catalina will not be subject to this Privacy Policy. For Information on how Catalina collects, shares and otherwise uses information it collects, go to its privacy policy located at http://www.couponnetwork.com/privacy.

### Information Collected Through Technology

In addition to any Personal Information or other information that you choose to submit to us, we and our third-party service providers may use a variety of technologies that automatically (or passively) collect certain information whenever you visit or interact with the Savings.com Applications, including without limitation, the URL that referred you to the Savings.com Applications (“Affiliate Referral Urls”) or other marketing or distribution sources, all of the areas within the Savings.com Applications that you visit, when you view, purchase, or redeem coupons or accept offers accessed through our Services, the comments you make through our Interactive Services, and how you otherwise use our Services and which offers are of interest to you (“Usage Information”). We may use the this Usage Information for a variety of purposes, including to enhance or otherwise improve the Savings.com Applications. In addition, we collect your IP address or other unique identifier (“Device Identifier”) for your computer or other device used to access the Savings.com Applications (any, a “Device”). A Device Identifier is a number that is automatically assigned to the Device used to access the Savings.com Applications, and our computers identify your Device by its Device Identifier. Usage Information may be non-identifying or may be associated with you. When you download and use our Brower Extensions we will also collect information from our affiliates and our merchants based upon the sites you visit, the coupons you redeem, and other web sites you may have visited or Affiliate Referral Urls and will store those Affiliate Referral Urls and a list of our merchants who provide savings through our Services on your Device to assist us in providing you with coupons and savings that are of interest to you. We will also collect Location information or Geolocation information to ensure we serve you offers and coupons for products and services available to you in your location. Whenever we associate Usage Information, Location information, Geolocation information or a Device Identifier with personally identifiable information, we will treat it as Personal Information.

A few of the tracking technologies that may be used to collect Usage Information include, without limitation, the following:

Cookies. A cookie is a data file placed on a Device when it is used to visit the Savings.com Applications. We use cookies to collect information for record keeping purposes, to make it easier to navigate the Savings.com Applications. Cookies are stored on users’ hard drives. We use both “session ID cookies” and “persistent cookies.” Session ID cookies are used to store information while a user is logged into the Site and expire when the user closes his/her browser. Persistent cookies are used to make tasks like logging into the Site easier for returning users by remembering a user’s login information. Persistent cookies stay on a user’s hard drive from one session to the next. Cookies may be used for many purposes, including, without limitation, remembering you and your preferences and tracking your visits to our web pages, merchant sites and redemption of coupons. When you click on a coupon or an offer on the “Savings.com Applications an affiliate cookie will be set on your hard drive to track your use and redemption of the coupon or offer. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a persistent or session cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off such cookies through your browser settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you choose to disable cookies on your Device, some features of the Savings.com Applications may not function properly.

Web Beacons. Small graphic images or other web programming code called web beacons (also known as “1×1 GIFs” or “clear GIFs”) may be included in our web pages and messages. Web beacons may be invisible to you, but any electronic image or other web programming code inserted into a web page or e-mail can act as a web beacon. Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including, without limitation, to count visitors to our Savings.com Applications, to monitor how users navigate the Savings.com Applications, to count how many e-mails that were sent were actually opened or to count how many particular articles or links were actually viewed.

Web Logs. Like most standard website servers, we log Device Identifiers and the operating system of your computer and may track your movement and redemption within the Savings.com Applications, the pages from which you were referred, access times and browser types in order to improve security, analyze trends and administer the Savings.com Applications. We use this information in the aggregate to gauge the effectiveness, usage, and popularity of our Savings.com Applications, track information for statistical purposes, help diagnose and troubleshoot server malfunctions, analyze trends, track user movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information and track traffic and sales to our partner merchants. We may also use individual information we collect through web logs to send you targeted offers and other communications.

### Information You Provide About a Third Party

If you send someone else a communication from the Savings.com Applications, such as sending an invitation to a friend, the information you provide (names, e-mail addresses, etc.) is used to facilitate the communication and is not used for any other marketing purpose unless we obtain consent from that person or we explicitly say otherwise. If that person becomes a customer or registers with us, his/her information will be treated in the same manner as all other customers or registered users. Please be aware that when you use any send-to-a-friend functionality on the Savings.com Applications, your e-mail address may be included in the communication sent to your friend.

### Information We Collect From Third Parties

We acquire information from other trusted sources to update or supplement the information you provided or we collected automatically, such as information to validate or update your address or other demographic and lifestyle information. We use this information to help us maintain the accuracy of the information we collect, to target our communications so that we can inform you of products, services and offers that may be of interest, and for internal business analysis or other business purposes.

### Third Party Analytics Technologies

We use third parties’ analytic and other tools to better understand who is using the Savings.com Applications, how people are using the Savings.com Applications and how to improve the effectiveness of the Savings.com Applications and its content, and to help those parties serve more targeted advertising to you across the Internet or help us serve more targeted savings to you. Those third party companies may use cookies, pixel tags or other technologies to collect and store anonymous information such as time of visit, pages visited, time spent on each page of the Savings.com Applications, Device Identifiers, type of operating system and browser used, Affiliate Referral URLs and other web sites you may have visited and will provide us with this information in part to help us understand and analyze shopping habits and other trends to enable us to improve our Services. They might combine information they collect from your interaction with Savings.com Applications with personal information they collect from other sources. We do not have access to, nor control over, third parties’ use of cookies or other tracking technologies. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third parties to see your options for opting out of their use of such devices. If you would like more information regarding which third party companies we use to provide these services who may be serving cookies or other tracking tools on our Savings.com Applications or want to know more about your choices about not having this anonymous collected or used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.savings.com/info/us/third-party-technologies/).

## II. HOW WE USE AND SHARE YOUR INFORMATION

Use of Information by Us. We may use Information that we collect about you: (1) to provide you with information or process transactions that you have requested or agreed to receive; (2) to provide you with information regarding new features, products or services; (3) to improve the Savings.com Applications or our Services and to customize your experience; (4) to contact you with regard to your use of the Savings.com Applications and, in our discretion, changes to the Savings.com Applications and/or the Savings.com Applications’ policies; (5) for internal business purposes; and (6) for purposes disclosed at the time you provide your information or as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy.

Transactional Communications. We may send you notices from time to time relating to your account or your orders. These may include order confirmations, invoices or customer service notifications. We may also send you service-related announcements when it is necessary to do so; for instance, if our Service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, or the delivery of a coupon is delayed or there is some service issue with something you may have ordered. You may not opt-out of receiving these communications, which are not promotional in nature.

Strategic Partners. We have entered into agreements with merchant partners to enable us to provide our Services in connection with sales of goods and services from our merchant partners, such as the redemption of coupons we provide on Savings.com Applications. In certain situations we may provide your information to those companies informing them of your registration or to investigate a claim or inquiry regarding any benefit you may make pertaining to our Services and your interactions with those companies. Since these third parties will use your information in accordance with their own privacy practices, you should check their websites for information regarding their respective privacy policies.

Service Providers. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Savings.com Applications or administer activities on our behalf. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes.

Electronic Promotional Offers. We may send you promotional emails regarding special offers about our Services or on behalf of third party marketing partners who we think can offer services and products of interest to you but we will not share your email address with any third parties. If you do not want to receive emails regarding special promotions or products or services, you may (i) Update your email preference Settings by visiting www.savings.com/, click on, clicking “Edit Profile” and then click on “Manage my notifications” and then selecting “None” under ” Newsletters”or (ii) Click the unsubscribe link in the body of any email.

Please note that even if you opt out of receiving promotional e-mails, we may continue to send you electronic service notifications that are related to your registration, your profile or other services you have requested.

Direct Mail Promotional Offers. We may sell, share or rent your name and mailing address and certain other information, such as what you ordered, with reputable companies that provide marketing offers through direct mail. If you do not want us to sell, rent or share your Personal Information with other companies so that they can send you direct mail offers about their products and services, please write to us at the street address set forth at the end of this document or click here. If you prefer not to have your name and mailing address shared with third parties, send an email to the above address with “No Rent” in the subject line. If you choose to opt-out via e-mail, please include “Direct Mail Opt-Out” in the subject line. Please note that even if you opt out of receiving promotional direct mail offers, we may continue to send you service notifications that are related to your account(s) and other products and services you have requested or in which you are currently enrolled by direct mail.

Third Party and Our Advertising. We use third-party ad servers and ad networks to serve advertisements and collect informationwhen you visit Savings.com Applications. These companies and the advertisers themselves may use information about your visits on other web sites and Savings.com Applications in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to Savings.com Applications, these third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your Device, the advertisements and links that appear on Savings.com Applications. They automatically receive your Device Identifier when this happens. They may also use tracking technologies to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content. We may also use information collected using third party cookies and Web beacons on Savings.com Applications and in our emails to deliver advertising about our Services displayed to you on third party websites. When you click on a coupon or an offer on the “Savings.com Applications an affiliate cookie will be set on your hard drive to track your use and redemption of the coupon or offer. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such advertisers, ad servers or ad networks. You should consult the respective privacy policies of any advertisers on Savings.com Applications to see your options for opting out of their use of such devices. In addition, some of the ad servers and ad networks may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies. If you opt-out of receiving targeted ads on Savings.com Applications from ad servers and ad networks, you may continue to receive advertising and promotional messages after you opt-out, but it will not be customized or personalized to you based on your use of our Savings.com Applications and/or third party websites. If you would like more information about advertisers’ use of tracking technologies and about your option not to accept the cookies used to track your activities and opt out, you can go to www.networkadvertising.org/choices. If you would like to learn more about how interest-based information is collected, whether the companies we use are part of an industry network regarding behavioral advertising and to know your choices about not having information used in this manner you can go to www.aboutads.info.

Co-branded Areas. Certain areas on our Savings.com Applications may be provided to you in association with third parties such as sponsors or advertisers which provide products and or services, such as rewards programs (“Co-Branded Areas”). Such Co-Branded Areas will identify the third party. If you elect to register for the products and/or services provided at these Co-Branded Areas, you either will be providing your Personal Information to both us and the third party or we might be providing your Personal Information directly to the third party in order for that third party to fulfill their products and services directly with you. Your Personal Information will be subject to this Privacy Policy as well as the privacy policy and practices of such third party. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of those third parties and we suggest you review the individual privacy policies of each company with whom you establish a relationship. You should consult the respective privacy policies of those third party sponsors or advertisers to learn more about their privacy practices.

Sweepstakes, Contests and Promotions. We may offer sweepstakes, contests, and other promotions (any, a “Promotion”) through the Savings.com Applications that may require registration. By participating in a Promotion, you are agreeing to official rules that govern that Promotion. If you choose to enter a Promotion, Personal Information may be disclosed to third parties or the public in connection with the administration of such Promotion and as required by law or permitted by the Promotion’s official rules.

Legal Matters; Safety. We may, without your consent, access and disclose your information, any communications sent or received by you (including, without limitation, the contents of any chat, messaging, or other communication posted in the Interactive Services), and any other information that we may have about you or your account as may be permitted or required by law (including, but not limited to, court order or subpoena), or to prevent or investigate suspected fraud, violations of our Terms of Service or activity that appears to us to be illegal or may expose us to legal liability. Additionally, we may disclose your information and/or communications in situations that we believe to be: (i) emergencies involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person or property if we believe that your information in any way relates to that threat; or (ii) your conduct on the Savings.com Applications or when using the Interactive Services that we believe is inappropriate and inconsistent with generally accepted norms of behavior.

Sale or Transfer of Business or Assets. In the event that we, or any of our businesses, are sold or disposed of as a going concern, whether by merger, sale of assets or otherwise, or in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership, personally identifiable information of our customers and visitors to our Savings.com Applications may be one of the assets sold or merged in connection with that transaction. Information about our customers and registered users may also need to be disclosed in connection with a commercial transaction where we or any one of our businesses are seeking financing, investment, support or funding. In such transactions, Personal Information will be subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy in effect when the information was obtained.

## III. ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION

If you have an account with us, you also may choose to resign and deactivate your account at any time. Please contact [Customer Care](https://savings.zendesk.com/home) or send an email with “Deactivate Account” in the subject line to [sara.d@savings.com](mailto:sara.d@savings.com). If you wish to change to modify information in your account please log in and visit your profile and click on “Edit Profile” . If for any reason you are concerned that the Personal Information you provided to us is not correct and you cannot change it by accessing your profile, or should you wish to have your street address or email address removed from our mailing list or contact information changed, please contact us at sara.d@savings.com. We will be happy to review, update or remove information as appropriate. If you deactivate your account, we may still retain certain information associated with your account for analytical purposes and recordkeeping integrity, as well as to prevent fraud, resolve disputes, enforce our Terms of Service or other policies, take actions we deem necessary due to technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the security, integrity and operation of our Savings.com Applications. In addition, if certain information has already been provided to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy, retention of that information will be subject to those third parties’ policies. We may still retain your information in our files however, to resolve disputes and enforce our Terms of Service.

## IV. CHOICE AND OPT OUT

You may remove your information from our database so as not to receive future communications or to close your account or opt out of our sharing information with third parties for marketing purposes by emailing us at sara.d@savings.com or sending postal mail (certified mail, return receipt requested is recommended) to the following postal address:

Savings.com, Inc.  
Attn: Customer Care  
2225 S Carmelina Avenue  
Los Angeles, CA 90064  
Attention: Privacy Administrator

If you prefer not to receive electronic promotional communications, you can also opt-out by following the unsubscribe instructions included in each communication.

Please note that changes may not be effective immediately. In each event, you must clearly indicate the information that you wish to have changed or clearly indicate that you wish to have your personally identifiable information removed from our database. We will endeavor to comply with your request as soon as reasonably possible. Note that despite any request for removal of or change to personally identifiable information, we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes and there may also be residual information that will remain within our databases and other records, which will not be removed or changed. Finally, we are not responsible for informing third parties (including without limitation our third party service providers or strategic partners) with whom we have already shared your personally identifiable information of any changes requested pursuant to this section, or for removing information from or causing information to be removed from the databases or records of such entities.

## V. IMPORTANT DISCLOSURES, PRACTICES AND CONTACT INFORMATION

Links to other Site and Communities. To the extent hyperlinks may be utilized to access external or third party sites and communities, you should be aware that these external or third party site and communities are not controlled by us and, therefore, are not subject to this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you check the privacy policies of each such site and community to determine how your personal information will be utilized by their proprietors.

Security. Please keep in mind that no data transmission over the Internet, wireless transmission or electronic storage of information can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and therefore we cannot ensure the security of any information you transmit to us, and your use of the Site indicates that you are willing to assume this risk.

Your California Privacy Rights (As provided by California Civil Code Section 1798.83)

California’s “Shine the Light” law, Civil Code section 1798.83, requires certain businesses to respond to requests from California customers asking about the business’ practices related to disclosing personal information to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. Alternately, such businesses may have in place a policy not to disclose personal information of customers to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes if the customer has exercised an option to opt-out of such information-sharing. We have such a policy in place. If you do not want us to send you emails regarding special promotions or offers or share your Personal Information with other companies so that they can send you emails about their products and services, simply follow the unsubscribe instructions that are located at the bottom of those emails or you can click here to [manage your email marketing preferences](http://www.savings.com/secure/member/profile/notify.html). If you do not want us to send you any offers from third parties through direct mail or share your Personal Information with other companies so that they can send you direct mail offers about their products and services, please write to us at the street address set forth at the end of this document or [click here](mailto:third_party_opt_out@savings.com). California customers may request further information about our approach to this law by contacting Customer Care or writing to us at the address below.

A Note To International Users. The Savings.com Applications are intended for use in the United States. If you are located anywhere outside of the United States, please be aware that information we collect will be transferred to, processed and stored in the United States. The data protection laws in the United States may differ from those of the country in which you are located, and your Personal Information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in the United States according to laws of the United States. By using the Savings.com Applications or providing us with any information, you consent to this transfer, processing and storage of your information in the United States. You are also consenting to the application of United States federal, and New York state law in all matters concerning the Site and this Privacy Policy.

Children’s Privacy. The Savings.com Applications are intended for a general audience and are not directed or intended for children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from individuals under 13 years of age. If you are under 13 years of age, you should not register or provide Personal Information on the Savings.com Applications. If we later obtain actual knowledge that a user is under 13 years of age, we will take steps to remove that user’s Personal Information from our systems.

Changes to the Privacy Policy. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most recent version of the Privacy Policy will always be posted on our Site, with the “Effective Date” posted at the top of the Policy. We may revise and update this Privacy Policy if our practices change, as technology changes, or as we add new Savings.com Applications or Community Services or change existing ones. If we make any material changes to our Privacy Policy or how we handle your Personal Information, you will know because the Effective Date of the Privacy Policy will change. If we are going to use any Personal Information in a manner that is materially different from that stated in our Privacy Policy at the time we collected such information, we will give you a reasonable opportunity to consent to the change. If you do not consent, your Personal Information will be used as agreed to under the terms of the privacy policy in effect at the time we obtained that information. By accessing the Savings.com Applications after the Effective Date, you are deemed to consent to our then-current privacy policy. We will use information previously obtained in accordance with the privacy policy in effect when the information was obtained from you.

Disputes. If you choose to visit the Savings.com Applications your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service including limitations on damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the laws of the United States, and the State of California.

No Rights of Third Parties. This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any Personal Information relating to users of the Site.

Contacting Us. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or the practices of the Savings.com Applications and Community Services, please send your email queries to [sara.d@savings.com](mailto:sara.d@savings.com) or write to us at:

Savings.com, Inc.  
Attn: Customer Care  
2225 S Carmelina Avenue  
Los Angeles, CA 90064  
Attention: Privacy Administrator

Copyright ©2012 Savings.com, Inc. All rights reserved.

Effective Date July 9th, 2012
